{
    "subject": "resource/The_Cable_Guy",
    "predicate": "property/editing",
    "object": "Steven Weisberg",
    "human_readable": "The Cable Guy was edited by Steven Weisberg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8351665139198303,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the editing style of Steven Weisberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990896105766296,
            "question": "Name the editor of the film 'The Cable Guy'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901982069015503,
            "question": "Who was responsible for editing 'The Cable Guy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7740495800971985,
            "question": "What role did Steven Weisberg have in the movie 'The Cable Guy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7697405815124512,
            "question": "Who edited the movie 'The Cable Guy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7560675740242004,
            "question": "Is Steven Weisberg known for editing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7462169528007507,
            "question": "What is the name of the editor for 'The Cable Guy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5020085573196411,
            "question": "Steven Weisberg worked on which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3821204602718353,
            "question": "What year was 'The Cable Guy' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34556058049201965,
            "question": "What other movies has Steven Weisberg worked on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Cable Guy was edited by Steven Weisberg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7186_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Cable Guy' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7186_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steven Weisberg worked on which film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7186_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the editor for 'The Cable Guy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7186_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7186_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The Cable Guy was edited by Steven Weisberg.\" Specifically, several documents mention Steven Weisberg's involvement as an editor in various films, including \"The Cable Guy\" (1996)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}